Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
- American Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Job security report, 1961; Publication (Box 279, Folder 7)
    Author: American Newspaper Guild. Dept. of Research & Information.
  - Item 2: Gentlemen and scholars of the press, Publication (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Collective bargaining manual, 1966; Publication (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Page 1 Dinner - Rochester Newspaper Guild Annual (1st), 1951; Publication (Box 279, Folder 7)
    Author: Rochester Newspaper Guild Annual
  - Item 5: Page 1 Dinner - Rochester Newspaper Guild Annual (6th), 1956; Publication (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Page 1 Dinner - Rochester Newspaper Guild Annual (7th), 1957; Publication (Box 279, Folder 7)
- American Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 279, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Issues & Evidence: guide to Guild-Post negotiations 1962, Publication (Box 279, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Contracts providing Severance Pay - 223 of 227 Contracts in effect, July 1, 1966, Publication (Box 279, Folder 8)
- American Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 279, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: $200 a week--now!: a report to the 1962 ANG wage conference, Publication (Box 279, Folder 9)
- American Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A history of 14 years of apathy, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Local Records a handbook for secretary-treasurers, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 1)
- American Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Would you play a game, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Seeing is believing, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The ANG Organizer -- An outline of the main elements of an argument for general wage increases by Morgan Hull, 1941; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Guildsmen All, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: $10,000,000 since V-J day!, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Thanks to the Guild, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: All together helps everyone, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Your Guild and you about Bread and Butter and self-respect, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: correspondence, 1950; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Guild News, 1949; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: As simple as ANG, 1946; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Current challenges to our free press, 1948; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 2)
- American Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Wire Service News - Bulletin(s) on Feb. Negotiations, 1949; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: article - Got a grievance, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: correspondence, 1951; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Bulletin No. 2, 1947; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 3)
- American Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Wages and conditions contracts, 1943; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Wages and conditions contracts, 1952; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Wages and conditions contracts, 1954; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: A report on two years of collective bargaining under the National Wage Program of the American Newspaper Guild: June 15, 1948, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 4)
- American Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Wages and conditions contracts, 1947; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 5)
- American Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Times-Guild Health Ins. Coverage, 1964; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 279.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Guild Reporter - articles, 1973-1977 (Box 279.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: article - The Newspaperman who founded a union, 1964; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Humanizing the VDT workplace: a health manual for local officers and stewards, 1981; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 6)
- American Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Page 1 Dinner - Rochester Newspaper Guild Annual (1st), 1951; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Page 1 Dinner - Rochester Newspaper Guild Annual (6th), 1956; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Page 1 Dinner - Rochester Newspaper Guild Annual (7th), 1957; Publication (Box 279.1, Folder 7)
- American Nurses Association (ANA), Publication (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Statement on training for health occupations, 1962; Publication (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: First, 1950; Publication (Box 280, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. 4, no. 11 (Mar. 1950)
  - Item 3: Patient care in the economic security program, Publication (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Chairing a local unit: manual for the Chairman of a local unit, Publication (Box 280, Folder 1)
- American Nurses Association (ANA), Publication (Box 280, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A Manual for an economic security program: a guide for state nurses associations, 1956; Publication (Box 280, Folder 2)
- American Nurses Association (ANA), Publication (Box 280, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Guidelines for the individual nurse contract, 1974; Publication (Box 280, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Correspondence, Publication (Box 280, Folder 3)
- American Nurses Association (ANA), Publication (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Guidelines for boards of inquiry, Publication (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Strike policy, Publication (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Organizing the local unit, Publication (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The grievance procedure, Publication (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Philosophy goals policies positions, Publication (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: ANA publications (Spring 76), Publication (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: This is ANA, Publication (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Nurses in action: a public relations manual, 1985; Publication (Box 280, Folder 4)
    Author: American Nurses Association. Commission on Economic and General Welfare
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Minimize union split, 1946-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Bank Union stops work 2 to 4 hours, 1946-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Office workers get new local charter, 1946-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Office union takes step toward formation of possible new leftist labor federation, 1946-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The Social workers' union replies, 1946-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Wing CIO office union to discipline communists, 1946-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Office union plans to file affidavits, 1946-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Asks CIO be enjoined, 1946-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: CIO sues union to recover loan, 1946-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Social unit breaks with leftist union, 1948-1951 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Union head denies saying a thing to Prudential about Communists, 1948-1951 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Union fights CIO ouster, 1948-1951 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: First ties in three capital US asks calming on Saar, 1948-1951 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: CIO lift-wingers lose, 1948-1951 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Urban league to drop 7, 1948-1951 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Union workers picket simplicity pattern fashion show at NYU, 1948-1951 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Office union takes step toward formation of possible new leftist labor federation, 1948-1951 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Man can't give falsies to girl, NLRB says, 1949-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Loew Employees vote for CIO, 1949-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Hancock increases agents' bay, 1949-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: CIO warns Loew's RKO, 1949-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Sign 2-year contract, 1949-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Film strike postponed, 1949-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Picket line halts Miller Shoe Plant, 1949-1950 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: The Pickets are gone, Publication (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Insurance agents win appeal on pay, Publication (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: 1 out of 5, Publication (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Your union guards your health, Publication (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: Do you need glasses, Publication (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: Only by joining the Union, Publication (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: In Union, there is health!, Publication (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: No Flu wanted, Publication (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: A Statement calling for a war health program, 1942; Publication (Box 281, Folder 1)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Know your union - outline material for classes in trade unionism, 1935; Publication (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Company Unionism in the suite collar field, Publication (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: A Legislative program for the New York Locals of the UOPWA (part II), 1940; Publication (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: A program for educational work in the unions, 1938; Publication (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: How we fight the depression, 1938; Publication (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Should social workers organize?, 1946; Publication (Box 281, Folder 2)
    Author: Clarence King
    Notes: Reprinted from The Woman's Press (Jan. 1946). 2 copies
  - Item 7: March 1938 Publication list, Publication (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: A union policy for insurance workers, 1938; Publication (Box 281, Folder 2)
    Author: Lewis Merrill
  - Item 9: White collar workers organize, 1938; Publication (Box 281, Folder 2)
    Author: Louis Gordon
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The FEOC Flash, 1937; Publication (Box 281, Folder 3)
    Notes: Oct. 21, 1937
  - Item 2: Mergers mean lay-offs!, Publication (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Job security and how to get it Financial Employees Organizing Committee, Publication (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Report of the General Executive Board to the. Constitutional Convention, 1942; Publication (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Report of the General Executive Board to the. Constitutional Convention, 1944; Publication (Box 281, Folder 3)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Career, 1949; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 5,6
  - Item 2: Insurance Career, 1942; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
    Notes: Supplement; vol. 1, no. 4
  - Item 3: Insurance Policy, 1937; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Agent's Voice, 1949; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Mr. and Mrs. Policyholder!, 1949; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: PRU delays elections, 1949; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: This is what Prudential wants, 1949; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Special Bulletin to Regional Directors and Organizers from James H. Durkin, 1949; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Who is telling the truth?, 1949; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: A message to you from President James H. Durkin and prudential Leaders, 1949; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: AFL joins Pru and NLRB in stalling the election!, 1949; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Statement to Local 59 Executive Board in support of UOPWA, 1949; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: March 18th is the date - Vote UOPWA!, 1949; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: PRU election flash, Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: A salary policy to win the war, 1943; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Metropolitan Management versus the agents the people and progress, 1948; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
    Author: Metropolitan Management
  - Item 17: Group Insurance Policy, Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: The case for the insurance plan, 1948; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: An Acturial analysis, Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: The strength of Gibraltar why a Prudential agent joined the union, Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: AFL-NFIA by its own record, 1948; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Portrait of a real union, 1948; Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: How to handle grievances and lead your local union, Publication (Box 281, Folder 4)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The plight of the white-collar unemployed: an urgent problem of the national government ..., 1939; Publication (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Legislative guide, Publication (Box 281, Folder 5)
    Author: United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA). Legislative Dept.
  - Item 3: Wage-Hour legislation and the white collar worker: the origin of suggested changes the intent of Congress social and economic implications of the act the proposed definitions and the UOPWA, 1940; Publication (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: National Legislative Program of the United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), CIO, 1940; Publication (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The health problem of the white collar worker: statement of the United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), 1939; Publication (Box 281, Folder 5)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Johannes Steel, 1945-1946 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Commercial Guild! Open House Party, 1945-1946 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Your own reconversion program at the Office and Professional School, 1945-1946 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The Office and Professional School, 1945-1946 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Saturday Bank closings!, 1945-1946 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: The CIO News - Jan. 22, 1945, Publication (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Union Acts - Oct. 1945, Publication (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Financial Employees - Guild News - vol.1, no.1 (Mar. 1945), Publication (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Screen Office and Professional Employees Guild Sound Track - Nov. 1945, Publication (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: 1540 - Feb. 16, 1946, Publication (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: It's as east as A-B-C: Handling a grievance is not mystery--, 1946; Publication (Box 281, Folder 6)
    Notes: flyer (photocopy)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Office Press Service, 1940; Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 2 (1940)
  - Item 2: Memo, 1939-1940 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 11, no.2, 12 (1939-1940)
  - Item 3: What membership in Local 16, UOPWA has to offer you, Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Welcome to Local 16, Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: These are your Committees!, Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Build a Union Library, Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: The President's Labor Day Message, Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Lowenstein Workers say - We've just begun to fight!, Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: correspondence, 1930-1949 (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Union Election results, 1937; Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Script, 1941; Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
    Notes: 19-May-41
  - Item 12: Local 16 Reports, 1937-1938 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    Notes: Oct. 1937-38
  - Item 13: Bulletin for Shop Treasurers, 1942; Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
    Notes: Apr- 42
  - Item 14: Progressive Office Worker (1937), Publication (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Local 16 Memo, 1938-1939 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 7,9-10, 13 (1938-1939)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 281, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Progressive Office Worker, 1958; Publication (Box 281, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 9 (Nov. 1958)
  - Item 2: correspondence, 1948; Publication (Box 281, Folder 8)
    Author: United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA)
  - Item 3: Wishing you a pleasant Labor Day weekend, Publication (Box 281, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Victory Action Letter; Come all UOPWA'rs, Publication (Box 281, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: 9 to 5, 1948; Publication (Box 281, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 3
  - Item 6: Report of the salary survey of the book publishing industry, 1940; Publication (Box 281, Folder 8)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Welfare, 1945-1946 (Box 281, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol. 9, no.3, 5 (1945, 1946)
  - Item 2: This is the SSEU, 1940-1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Closed, Are you a Social Security step-child?, 1940-1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Preferred employment practices in social agencies, 1940-1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: The SSEU its purpose and program, 1940-1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: The SSEU by, for and of Employees in Social Agencies, 1940-1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Call to a Greater New York Welfare Mobilization, 1940-1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: An index to the cost of living, 1940-1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Social Service Employees Union announces a Professional program, 1940-1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: The Case of Mary, 1940-1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: This is your union, 1940-1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: By-laws of Local 19, 1940-1949 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: We lay our union cards on the table, 1948; Publication (Box 281, Folder 9)
    Author: United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA). Local No. 19
  - Item 14: Collective bargaining in social work, 1938; Publication (Box 281, Folder 9)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The News Letter, 1940; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Author: Social Service Employees Union. Local 19
    Notes: vol. 4, no. 1-2, 4-5, 7
  - Item 2: News, 1941; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Author: Social Service Employees Union
    Notes: vol. 5, no.3
  - Item 3: Field and Office, 1937; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 8
  - Item 4: Field and Office, 1938; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 2, 6
  - Item 5: Welfare, 1943; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Notes: no. 11
  - Item 6: Chapter Views, 1941; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Author: Social Service Employees Union. Community Service Society Chapter
    Notes: Aug. 13, 1941
  - Item 7: Chapter Views, 1941; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Notes: Nov. 26, 1941
  - Item 8: In and out of the CIO with the Social Work Unions, 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Memorandum for Chapter Chairman, 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: What's happening to Social Security?, 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Union Action Letter, 1946-1949 (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.167, 169-172, 175-176
  - Item 12: Guild News, 1939; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 11, no. 5
  - Item 13: The News Letter, 1939; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 8, 17
  - Item 14: Common Welfare, 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: For all employees and employers in Social Service, 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Support the National Labor Relations Act..., 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Re: your salary.., 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: For maintenance workers..., 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Stop the march toward poverty & war..., 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Who's who on the 1941-42..., 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: For election of Officers..., 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Invitation to disaster!, 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: Be our guest at a conference..., 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Adventures of Delphinium..., 1938-1944 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Social Service Employees Union, War program for the mobilization, Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: correspondence, 1943; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Author: Social Service Employees' Union
  - Item 27: Chapter Views, 1940; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 4, 6, 8
  - Item 28: Chapter Views, 1941; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 2, no.4-6
  - Item 29: Draft By-Laws of Local #19 of the United Office and Professional Workers, 1936; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 30: Procedures for union negotiations in a social agency, Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 31: Statement on peace endorsed by the SSEU, 1940; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 32: Contract with SSEU Local 19, 1940; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
    Author: National Council of Jewish Women
  - Item 33: Defense of what?, 1940; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Item 34: This is not a ballot, final official notice on Annual Election of Officers and Executive, 1943; Publication (Box 281, Folder 10)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Caught in the act, Publication (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: You too, can help organize, Publication (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Success story, Publication (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Stewards Bulletin, 1949; Publication (Box 282, Folder 1)
    Notes: Mar. 15, 1949. 2 copies
  - Item 5: The adventures of Agent Truboy, Publication (Box 282, Folder 1)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 282, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Carbon Copy, 1948; Publication (Box 282, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 7, no. 1, 5-6, 9- 11
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: You are a union man!, Publication (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: We sell security, Publication (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Spotlight, 1946; Publication (Box 282, Folder 3)
    Notes: no. 1 (Oct. 1946)
  - Item 4: Insurance Outlook, 1945; Publication (Box 282, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 7 (1945)
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 282, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Insurance Outlook, 1947-1948 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 4, no. 5-11 (1947-1948)
- Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), Publication (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: You have a right to know the facts, Publication (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Social Security for Social Service Employees, Publication (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Union Standards, Publication (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Two Key Meetings, Publication (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: It's our fight too!, Publication (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: News for SSEU Members, 1940; Publication (Box 282, Folder 5)
    Notes: Jun-40
- United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), Publication (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Welcome to SOPEG, Publication (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Call Joint screen office and Professional Employees, Wage and policy conference, Publication (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: World Penicillin help the cancer in Loew's, Publication (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Can Paramount afford to give its employees a $10 raise?, Publication (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Congratulations, Publication (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Fall Program 1942-43, Publication (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: The Coal Crisis, Publication (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: The Railroad Strike, Publication (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: National Screen to meet "SOPEG", Publication (Box 282, Folder 6)